Guide to the Leonard S. Marcus Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2015 Acquisition, circa 1850-2015; circa 1975-2015; 110.08; (98 boxes)
  - Writings, circa 1981-2015; 77.5; (68 boxes)
    - Short Works, circa 1981-2015
      - Parenting Magazine, circa 1987-2008
        - Reading Magic Awards, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1119)
        - Reading Magic Awards, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1120)
        - February 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1121)
        - March 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1122)
        - April 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1123)
        - Interview with Jon Scieszka and Lane Smith, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 1124)
        - May 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1125)
        - June/July 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1126)
        - August 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1127)
        - September 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1128)
        - October 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1129)
        - November 2001 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1130)
        - December 2001/January 2002 reviews, 2001–2002 (Box 46, Folder 1131)
        - Febraury 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1132)
        - March 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1133)
        - April 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1134)
        - May 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1135)
        - June/July 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1136)
        - August 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1137)
        - September 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1138)
        - October 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1139)
        - November 2002 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1140)
        - Reading Magic Awards, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1141)
        - Parenting.com interview, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1142)
        - Parenting.com Book Awards interview, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 1143)
        - My Brother Martin sidebar review, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1144)
        - February 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1145)
        - March 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1146)
        - Journal books sidebar, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1147)
        - Q&A, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1148)
        - April 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1149)
        - May 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1150)
        - June/July 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1151)
        - August 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1152)
        - September 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1153)
        - October 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1154)
        - November 2003 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1155)
        - Best Books Awards, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 1156)
        - February 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1157)
        - March 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1158)
        - April 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1159)
        - May 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1160)
        - June 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1161)
        - July 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1162)
        - August 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1163)
        - September 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1164)
        - October 2004 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1165)
        - Best Books Awards, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 1166)
        - March 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1167)
        - April 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1168)
        - May 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1169)
        - June 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1170)
        - July 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1171)
        - August 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1172)
        - September 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1173)
        - October 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1174)
        - November 2005 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1175)
        - Best Books Awards, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 1176)
        - Parenting and Entertainment Weekly interview with Maurice Sendak, circa 1987-2005 (Box 49, Folder 1244)
        - Review of Dear Mili, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 1245)
        - Coretta Scott King Award sidebar, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 1248)
        - Parenting interview xeroxes, circa 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1249)
        - Parenting sixth column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1602)
        - Parenting seventh column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1603)
        - Parenting eighth column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1604)
        - Parenting fifth column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 59, Folder 1605)
      - Other Short Works and Events, circa 1981-2015
        Documents the research, writing, and publication of Marcus's short works, including articles, forewords, and talks. Includes research materials, notes, drafts, correspondence, publicity, and clippings.
        - Ezra Jack Keats awards, 2000–2001 (Box 3, Folder 48)
        - Motoo Ito, circa 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 393-395)
        - Eric Carle essay for Japan, circa 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 396)
        - Japan talk, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 397)
        - Gifts to children Japan essay, circa 1999-2004 (Box 15, Folder 398)
        - Motoo Ito, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 399)
        - "In and Out of the Secret Garden: How the American Picture Book Grew," Japan talk, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 400)
        - Japan research, 2010 (Box 15, Folder 401-402b)
        - David Weisner NCCIL exhibition, circa 1990-2000 (Box 18, Folder 436)
        - Interview with Margaret K. McElderry, The Horn Book Magazine, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 437-438)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, Ed Young gallery guide, circa 1990-2000 (Box 18, Folder 439)
        - Book Magazine museums article, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 440)
        - Walden Media, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 441)
        - Charlotte's Web Walden Media essay, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 442)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Awards, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 443)
        - Gale Sendak reprint, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 444)
        - Children's Books in Children's Hands "Ask the Critic" feature, circa 2005-2007 (Box 18, Folder 445)
        - Writing weekly reader interview, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 449)
        - Curious George film, Universal/Cowen, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 450)
        - "The Ursula Nordstrom Tapes," The Horn Book Magazine, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 451)
        - Walter Wick exhibition, New Britain Museum of American Art, circa 1990-2006 (Box 18, Folder 452)
        - The New York Times Book Review picture book biographies, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 453)
        - The New York Times Book Review moving books, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 454)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of City Seen from A to Z by Rachel Isadora, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 455)
        - The New York Times Book Review, Elisha Cooper and Cynthia Rylant, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 456)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of annual picture books, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 457)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of The Wall by Peter Sís, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 458)
        - The New York Times Book Review New York City books, circa 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 459)
        - The New York Times Book Review Walter Dean Myers reviews, circa 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 460)
        - The New York Times Book Review darkness books, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 461)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of The Chronicles of Harris Burdick, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 462)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Animal Masquerade, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 463)
        - The New York Times Book Review, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 464)
        - The New York Times Book Review frog books, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 465)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Applesauce Season by Eden Ross Lipson, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 466)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Marching for Freedom, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 467)
        - The New York Times Book Review animal photography books, circa 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 468)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Runny Babbit, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 469)
        - The New York Times Book Review Christmas 2002 books (Box 18, Folder 470)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Once There Was a Tree by Natalia Romanova, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 471)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Little Lit, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 472)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Judith Viorst, circa 2000-2008 (Box 18, Folder 473)
        - My World: A Companion to Goodnight Moon, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 605)
        - The New York Times Book Review, Margaret Wise Brown essay, circa 1999-2008 (Box 27, Folder 606)
        - Barnes and Noble introductions, circa 1990-1998 (Box 28, Folder 613)
        - Horn Book columns, circa 2010-2014 (Box 28, Folder 614-626)
        - The Complete Works of Lewis Carroll introduction, Barnes and Noble edition, circa 1994 (Box 28, Folder 627)
        - Mother Goose's Little Misfortunes introduction, circa 1990 (Box 28, Folder 628)
        - Obituaries and other clips of interest, circa 1990-2000 (Box 28, Folder 629)
        - The Wind in the Willows introduction, circa 1995 (Box 28, Folder 630)
        - The Wonderful Wizard of Oz introduction, Barnes and Noble edition, circa 1995 (Box 28, Folder 631)
        - Ezra Jack Keats awards, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 632)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature, 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 633)
        - Cannibal in the Mirror study guide questions, circa 2000 (Box 28, Folder 634)
        - Children's Book Council, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 635)
        - Amazon.com authors' favorite books, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 636-637)
        - Abrams proposal, circa 1990-2000 (Box 28, Folder 638)
        - The Penguin Book of Classic Children's Characters, circa 1998 (Box 28, Folder 639)
        - Margaret Wise Brown speech, Bibliothèque nationale de France, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 640)
        - Ladybug biography of Margaret Wise Brown, circa 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 641)
        - The New York Times Book Review, essay on Goodnight Moon, circa 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 642)
        - Children's Book Council article on Goodnight Moon, circa 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 643)
        - Children's Literature Association conference, Margaret Wise Brown panel, circa 1995-2000 (Box 28, Folder 649)
        - "Getting a Life: Some Thoughts on Writing Margaret Wise Brown's (or Anyone's) Biography", circa 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 655)
        - Ezra Jack Keats lecture, Donnell Central Children's Room, circa 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 658)
        - Margaret Wise Brown entry, A Reader's Companion to Twentieth Century Children's and Young Adult Literature, circa 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 659)
        - Dictionary of Literary Biography, Margaret Wise Brown essays, circa 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 660)
        - Petrouchka: A Ballet Cut-Out Book, David R. Godine, Jane Kendall, circa 1984 (Box 29, Folder 661)
        - Continuum Encyclopedia of Children's Literature, Margaret Wise Brown article, circa 2005 (Box 29, Folder 662)
        - Zimmerli Museum, Rutgers, circa 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 666)
        - American Library Association, 1993–1994 (Box 29, Folder 667)
        - Margaret Wise Brown correspondence, circa 1988-1999 (Box 30, Folder 668-669)
        - The Borrowers anniversary edition foreword, circa 2003 (Box 36, Folder 801)
        - The Borrowers research material from Harcourt files, circa 2003 (Box 36, Folder 802-803)
        - Petrouchka book of paper toys with Risa Breslau, circa 1984 (Box 36, Folder 806)
        - "Medal Man: Randolph Caldecott and the Art of the Picture Book," The Horn Book Magazine, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 846-847)
        - Wendell Minor essay, Norman Rockwell museum, circa 2013 (Box 38, Folder 848)
        - Pop-up exhibition, Print Center, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 849)
        - Tomi Ungerer column, The Horn Book Magazine, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 850)
        - "The Reulctant Dragon" introduction, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 851)
        - Fred Marcellino article, Fine Books Magazine, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 852)
        - Fred Marcellino exhibition, Norman Rockwell Museum, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 853)
        - Bank Street publications office, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 854)
        - Teachers TV, BBC, 2008 (Box 38, Folder 855)
        - Century exhibition, The Phantom Tollbooth event, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 856)
        - Seven Stories, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 857)
        - Decatur Book Festival, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 858)
        - Vancouver children's literature roundtable, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 859)
        - National Book Festival, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 860)
        - Hartford History Center Project, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 861)
        - Highlights workshop, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 862)
        - Maryland Institute College of Art, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 863)
        - Augusta Baker's Dozen Festival, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 864)
        - Kentucky Book Festival, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 865)
        - Church of the Heavenly Rest, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 866)
        - Beatrix Potter Society talk, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 867)
        - Children's Books as Literature class, The New School for Social Research, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1006)
        - Children's Literature for Illustrators class, School of Visual Arts, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1007)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of The Treasures of Childhood: Books, Toys, and Games from the Opie Collection, circa 1989 (Box 45, Folder 1008)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Pish, Posh, Said Hieronymus Bosch, circa 1991 (Box 45, Folder 1009)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of One, Five, Many, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1010)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of The Incredible Painting of Felix Clousseau, circa 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1011)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Rechenka's Eggs, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1012)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Beatrix Potter: Artist, Storyteller, and Countrywoman, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1013)
        - Smithsonian Magazine, review of An Odd Bestiary, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 1014)
        - National Public Radio reviews, circa 1985-1999 (Box 45, Folder 1015)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Foundation New Writer Award, 1999–2000 (Box 47, Folder 1177)
        - C-SPAN 2 and Book TV, circa 1985-1999 (Box 47, Folder 1178)
        - American Library Association and Children's Book Council panel discussion, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1179)
        - American Library Association, New Orleans, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1180)
        - Enoch Pratt Free Library, Baltimore, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 1181)
        - "The Art of Reading," Corcoran Gallery, Washington, D.C., circa 1995-1999 (Box 47, Folder 1182)
        - Talk at Perrot Library, Old Greenwich, Connecticut, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 1183)
        - Irma and James Black Award breakfast talk, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 1184)
        - "The Picture Book: Art, Innovation, and Experiment," The New School for Social Research, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1185)
        - Weston Woods Institute, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 1186)
        - Simmons College Summer Institute talk, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1187)
        - Fordham University, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 1188)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Award, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 1189)
        - Children's Library Association of Suffolk County, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 1190)
        - Christian Science Monitor, review of children's poetry books, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1191)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature conference, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 1192)
        - Society of Illustrators talk, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1193)
        - Norman Rockwell Museum, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1194)
        - National Council of Teachers of English, Denver, Colorado, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 1195)
        - NYU Conference, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1196)
        - "Reading and the Child," Boston Athenaeum, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1197)
        - NYU publishing seminar talk, circa 1990-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1198)
        - American Library Association preconference, Chicago, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 1199)
        - School Library Media Specialists of Southeastern New York Conference, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 1200)
        - Library of Congress interview about Robert McCloskey, circa 1990-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1201)
        - Hotel Boy photography exhibition, circa 1990-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1202)
        - Norman Rockwell Museum children's book symposium, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1203)
        - Free Library of Philadelphia, circa 1990-2000 (Box 47, Folder 1204)
        - University of Tennessee, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 1205)
        - Brooklyn Children's Museum symposium on children's books, sleep, and dreams, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1206)
        - American Library Association conference, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1207)
        - Society of Children's Books Writers and Illustrators conference, Hofstra, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1208)
        - The Horn Book Magazine interview with Bill Morris, circa 1995-2005 (Box 47, Folder 1209)
        - "Looking-Glass Modernist: Charles Green Shaw and the Making of No Such Animal," Archives of American Art Journal, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 1210)
        - Publishers Weekly Margaret Wise Brown article, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 1211)
        - "Humor and the Spirit of Play," The Lion and the Unicorn, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1212)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of The Snow Cat by Dayal Kaur Khalsa, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1213)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Simon's Book by Henrik Drescher, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1214)
        - The New York Times Book Review, review of Beauty and the Beast by Warwick Hutton, circa 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1215)
        - Anita Silvey Profiles in Courage project, 2008–2009 (Box 48, Folder 1216)
        - Something about the author, circa 2008-2010 (Box 48, Folder 1217)
        - Publishers Weekly, review of Silly Lilly and the Four Seasons by Agnès Rosenstiehl, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 1218)
        - Meridian exhibition, 2005–2006 (Box 48, Folder 1219-1220)
        - Children's Book of the Month Club, circa 2008-2010 (Box 48, Folder 1221)
        - Esphyr Slobodkina essay, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 1222)
        - Virginia Lee Burton quote for Vogue, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 1223)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Awards, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 1224-1226)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature Wendell Minor exhibition, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 1227)
        - Don Freeman anthology, Penguin, circa 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 1228-1229)
        - Reading is Fundamental, The Art of Reading foreword, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 1230-1231)
        - Reading is Fundamental, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 1232)
        - Paul Galdone anthology Clarion Books, circa 2001 (Box 48, Folder 1233)
        - Meridian International Center, circa 2001-2005 (Box 48, Folder 1234-1235)
        - Ghent Magazine, circa 2001-2005 (Box 48, Folder 1236)
        - Ezra Jack Keats Awards, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 1237)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of picture books, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1238)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of picture books by poets, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1239)
        - Smithsonian Magazine, review of Redesigning the World: William Morris, the 1880s, and the Arts and Crafts, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 1240)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of Anno's Mysterious Multiplying Jar, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1241)
        - Ezra Jack Keats talk, University of Southern Mississippi children's literature conference, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 1242)
        - Ezra Jack Keats talk at the Brooklyn Public Library, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 1243)
        - American Library Association catalog, 1994–1995 (Box 49, Folder 1246)
        - Jean George interview, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1247)
        - Interview with Allen Say, The Horn Book Magazine, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1250)
        - Press, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1251-1252a)
        - The Washington Post Book World, children's book round-up, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 1253)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of Yellow & Pink by William Steig, and Treehorn's Wish by Heide and Gorey, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1254)
        - Lewis Carroll review, Children's Literature, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1255)
        - Henry Steig, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1256)
        - The Washington Post Book World, picture book reviews, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1257)
        - The Washington Post Book World, artists' books and illustrated books, circa 1984 (Box 49, Folder 1258)
        - David R. Godine, Godine storytellers research, circa 1980-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1259)
        - The Washington Post Book World, review of Light Verse, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 1260)
        - Interview with Amy Schwartz, The Horn Book Magazine, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1261)
        - Anno essay, The Lion and the Unicorn, picture book issue, 1983–1984 (Box 49, Folder 1262)
        - White House book project, circa 1985-1995 (Box 49, Folder 1263)
        - Introduction to The Art of Eric Carle, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1264)
        - I Saw Esau program, Teachers College, Columbia University, with Iona Opie and Maurice Sendak, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 1265)
        - National Center for Children's Illustrated Literature Pinkneys exhibition note, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1266)
        - Children's Literature New England, 1999-2002 (Box 49, Folder 1267-1268)
        - Brooklyn Public Library statement, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1269)
        - Teachers College, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1270)
        - National Book Award, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1271)
        - Books for Kids Foundation Margaret Wise Brown plaque at Bank Street, circa 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 1272)
        - Loose Leaf Book Company, Margaret Wise Brown conversation with Tom Bodette, circa 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 1273)
        - Loose Leaf Book Company, review of The Boy of a Thousand Faces by Brian Selznick, circa 1995-2001 (Box 49, Folder 1274)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 1275)
        - Bank Street College of Education, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 1276)
        - Reading Rainbow contest, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 1277)
        - Morgan Library talk, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 1278)
        - American Library Association conference, San Francisco, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 1279)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 1280)
        - Society of Printers, Boston, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 1281)
        - Blue Levy TV interview, circa 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 1282)
        - BookExpo America, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 1283)
        - Notes from Asia trip, 2014 (Box 50, Folder 1284)
        - Asian Festival of Children's Content, circa 2014 (Box 50, Folder 1285)
        - Sweden trip, 2013 (Box 50, Folder 1286)
        - Paris and Copenhagen trip, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 1287)
        - Trip to Japan and Singapore, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 1288)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators Paris conference, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 1289)
        - Asian Festival of Children's Content, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 1290)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, Bologna, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 1291-1292)
        - Bologna trip, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 1293)
        - Paris trip, circa 2008-2010 (Box 50, Folder 1294)
        - Ragazzi Prize, Bologna, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 1295)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, Paris, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 1296)
        - Society of Children's Book Writers and Illustrators conference, Bologna, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 1297)
        - Alice's Adventures in Wonderland introduction, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 1298-1303)
        - Mary Engelbreit's Fairy Tales introduction, circa 2010 (Box 51, Folder 1316)
        - Mary Engelbreit poems, circa 2005-2010 (Box 51, Folder 1317)
        - Mary Engelbreit's Mother Goose introduction, circa 2005 (Box 51, Folder 1318)
        - Mary Engelbreit, circa 2005-2010 (Box 51, Folder 1319)
        - Mary Engelbreit's Mother Goose, circa 2005 (Box 51, Folder 1320)
        - George M. Nicholson memorial, 2015 (Box 52, Folder 1321)
        - Listening Library interview with Robert Cormier, circa 1995-2015 (Box 52, Folder 1322)
        - David Macaulay interview, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 1323)